(soothing music)
Welcome back to the final project of this course.
And in this one, we take everything that we learned
throughout the course and put it all into one beautiful,
modern, and really advanced application.
So we're gonna use things like classes, modules, promises,
a single weight, parcel and so much more.
Also we're gonna dive even deeper into flow charts
and project architecture in this project
so that you become more and more confident and prepared
to actually write applications by yourself.
So, this will be a ton of work, but also a lot of fun
and so I can't wait to finally show you this project now.
(upbeat music)